couchtuner.video 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Couchtuner TV Video

**Imp : New Domain  Couchtuner.Video | Spread the Word | Last Updated: September 3, 2016 at 10:10 am **   

**Last Modified:** September 3, 2016 at 10:10 am  
**Author:** [Couchtuner](https://plus.google.com/+CouchTunerMe/?rel=author)

**Privacy Policy**

It gives viewers information on personal stuffs collected or left on the site. Take time to read the privacy policy before watching your favorite TV SHOWS or submitting any information. Using the site, we assume that you have read and understand the policy.

**Information Collected/Left**

Information is collected only if users submitted the information voluntarily. The information such as name, email address, etc are used to send replies to specific requests, unless the user grant the administrator the permission to use the information in other matters such as mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

CouchTuner may use tracking and/or cookies technology, useful for collecting data like operating system, checking the number of viewers, browser type, and the site’s usefulness to its users. Your personal information can’t be gathered using this technology; on the other hand, if you previously provided your personal information, cookies may link back to that information. Our advertisers or other third parties may use cookies to collect data to provide specific ads. Most of the browsers automatically recognize cookies, but you may modify your browser settings to decline cookies.

**Information Distribution**

Information provided on the site is secured and is not provided to any third party individuals for marketing gains. For companies investigating frauds or other government agencies, we may share information with appropriate documents or concerns, e.g. protecting individuals due to fraud issues, required and permitted by the law and other fraud concerns.

**Our Commitment to Data Safety**

Information provided on the site is kept safe and secured. Authorized and reliable staffs (who understand and values information security) can see and have access to the information provided. We may send emails and newsletters and it includes option whether you agree or not to receive future mails from us.

**Concerns on Privacy and Data Security**

For concerns, questions or comments, contact us at

**admin[at]couchtuner.bz**

**Changes are made to this policy without asking further permission from its users. You have to check and read the privacy policy from time to time to make sure that you understand the information posted on this page or the privacy policy.**
